http://www.specialtybottle.com/privacy-policy/

We are only accepting orders from existing customers at this time. See details and instructions for placing orders here
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy explains the manner in which Specialty Bottle collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the www.specialtybottle.com site. This privacy policy applies to our site and all products and services offered by Specialty Bottle Supply LLC and Specialty Bottle Inc.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, register on the site, place an order and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and payment information.
We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from placing an order or engaging in certain site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about the means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our site uses "cookies" to enhance user experience. A user’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Our online services use two types of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies only exist while your browser is open. We use session cookies for website functionality, such as managing items added to your shopping cart. Persistent cookies are not removed when you exit your web browser. We use persistent cookies to enable an easier log-in process, provide you with a more personalized shopping experience, and help you navigate our website more efficiently. We also use persistent cookies to show you the items you have previously browsed. A user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Specialty Bottle collects and uses information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service we may use your information to help us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To personalize user experience we may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.
To improve our site we may use information and feedback to improve our website offerings.
To provide relevant advertising we may use cookie information to provide relevant advertising (see sharing cookie information below)
To process transactions we may use the personal information users provide about themselves when placing an order to service that order. We may provide such information to third party service providers to help us service that order.
To send periodic emails the email address users provide will be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. Users may also receive emails that may include information about abandoned carts, company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future promotional emails, we include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of such emails.
Disclosure of your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information and data.
Sensitive and private data exchange between our site and users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Be advised, no security safeguards or standards are guaranteed to provide 100% security. You should always use appropriate self-protection measures and practice safe browsing on all websites.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to others. We may provide your information to third party service providers to help us operate our business and the site or administer activities on our behalf. For example, if your order is being shipped via UPS, we will share your address and phone number with UPS to facilitate delivery of your product. We may share information to comply with a legal order, to protect against legal liability of the company, to investigate a potential fraud or in connection with the sale or transfer of all or a part of our business. We may share generic aggregated demographic or summary information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners and advertisers.
Sharing cookie information
The site uses third-party vendors, including Google and Microsoft, which use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. These ads may also contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our site, cookies received with banner or other ads are collected by the company displaying the ads, and we do not have access to this information. For further information regarding the privacy practices of Google and opting out of Google’s use of cookies, please visit www.google.com. For further information regarding the privacy practices of Microsoft and opting out of Microsoft’s use of cookies, please visit www.microsoft.com.
Third party websites
Users may access content on our site that link to the sites and services of our partners and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
Specialty Bottle has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date on this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. This policy was last updated on January 27, 2020.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of our site, or your dealings with our site, please contact us at:
Specialty Bottle www.specialtybottle.com 3434 4th Avenue S Seattle, WA 98134 (206) 382-1100 service@specialtybottle.com
Your cart is empty.
From Martha Stewart and others using our bottles, jars, and tins.
×
